<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Witec at Syracuse</title>
    <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Witec at Syracuse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:57:54 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1st  Syracuse Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Research Workshop</title>
      <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/blockchain_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:57:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/blockchain_workshop/</guid>
      <description>1st Syracuse Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Research Workshop August 16-18, 2021 (Virtual &amp;amp; In Person at Syracuse University) Event Recap Thank you to everyone who was able to join, participate, and contribute to creating an incredible event. Below you can find recordings of Day 1 and Day 2 with the full event details below that.
Day 1 The recording for Day 1 can be found here.
Day 2 The recording for Day 2 can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Poster</title>
      <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 16:59:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/poster/</guid>
      <description>Poster </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Backpack</title>
      <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/internet-backpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 16:59:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/internet-backpack/</guid>
      <description>Internet Backpack The Imcon Internet Backpack is the always-on, self-sustaining Internet Backpack with one-touch, self-initiating features. Imcon product solutions offer the mobility and flexibility to connect everyone from first responders, remote working, remoted learning &amp;amp; education, users in stressed or degraded environments, and those in remote locations across the globe to the world’s digital ecosystem. The Internet Backpack comes with innovative technology that allows for connections to multiple network types and allowing access on up to 90% of the planet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Escape Room</title>
      <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/ver/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:58:55 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/ver/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Escape Room This is one of the many fun events you will get to participate in as a part of Witec. You’re locked inside a room built by blockchain and cloud scientists, and have an hour to escape from it – and the only way to escape is by finding the clues around the room. The faster you escape from the room, the bigger the rewards! This story follows one of the biggest cyber scandals surrounding the dark web and cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Internet Connectivity in Liberia</title>
      <link>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/liberia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 16:57:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://witec-cuse.github.io/witec/portfolio/liberia/</guid>
      <description>iSchool to Lead Partnership Expanding Internet Connectivity in Liberia The School of Information Studies (iSchool), Imcon International and the Republic of Liberia will collaborate on the 40 in 2021 Project, a far-reaching initiative that will digitally transform the country of Liberia by increasing the nation’s current Internet penetration of about 7 percent to 40 percent by 2021. The announcement was made Thursday by Elizabeth D. Liddy, dean of the iSchool, and Rob Loud, CEO of Imcon International Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
